Interfaith Worker Justice Records 6414
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Jaime Rapaport, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Lauren Beth Thomas, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Andrew Schwiebert, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Anshi Zachariah, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Simeon Akoete, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Ranjit Mathews, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Matthew Carl (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Jeffrey Clinger, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Arrey Besong Joseph, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Batetataw Mercy Beyang, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Masha Savitz, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Sabira Alloo, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Kim Crawford, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Tynisha Drennon, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Darrell Ezell, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Brian Gleichauf, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Cynthia Griffin, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- David Henley, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Selina Jarrett, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Rebecca Johnson, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Nina Kalmoutis, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Aqel Khan, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Eliza Kukla, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Matthew Lang, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Fransiskus Magung, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Amisha Patel, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Elsa Peters, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Jeremy Posadas, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- Gregory Potts, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Ann Pratt, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Dawn Price, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Robin Bagsdale, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- Bridie Roberts, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Margaret Sawyer, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Sandra Schmidt, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 84)
- Jennifer Seaich, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 85)
- Tasneem Siddiqui, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 86)
- Catherine "Rafi" Simonton, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 87)
- Christopher Soh, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 88)
- David Soliday, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 89)
- William Van Doren, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 90)
- Gila Ward, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 91)
- Melissa Woodforlk, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 92)
- Alison Abrams, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 93)
- Junaid Sirat Ahmad, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 94)
- Manikka Bowman, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 95)
- Adam Bray, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 96)
- John Brisco, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 97)
- Beverly Brown, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 98)
- Benjamin John Caduff, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 99)
- Paula Cripps, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 100)
- Mamoudou Diarra, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 101)
- Tiffany Dupree, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 102)
- Judy Esber, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 103)
- Jessica Lynn Fertig, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 104)
- Aaron Fine, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 105)
- Brian Fink, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 106)
- John Flack, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 107)
- Krystal Grant, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 108)
- Mark Hardin, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 109)
- Leah Hart-Landsberg, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 110)
- Earnestine Hunt, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 111)
- Troy Jacobson, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 112)
- Margie Klein, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 113)
- Sang-Il Kim, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 114)
- Sarah Marie Knapp, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 115)
- Chaim Koritzinksy, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 116)
- Kristi Laughlin, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 117)
- J. Charles Lockett, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 118)
- James Luvene, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 119)
- Lauri Maben, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 120)
- Katie McKay, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 121)
- Felicia Moller, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 122)
- Jerad Morey, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 123)
- Andrew Plocher (Box 8, Folder 124)
- Eliza Denise Royal, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 125)
- Lerlene Santoyo, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 126)
- Sameerah Siddiqui, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 127)
- Nathan Tenney, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 128)
- Colin Theis, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 129)
- Amanda Tomkins, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 130)
- Jackeline Vives, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 131)
- Josh Wohl, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 132)
- Michelle Dardashti, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 133)
- Michael Diaz, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 134)
- Sarah Friedson, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 135)
- Michael Goodman, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 136)
- Ben Greenberg, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 137)
- Gulsum Gurbuz, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 138)
- Andrew Highland, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 139)
- Ayse Kaplan, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 140)
- Patricia Keteltas, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 141)
- Joshua Lawrence, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 142)
- Fred Lesakale, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 143)
- Steven Lewis, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 144)
- April Lewton, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 145)
- Madeline Lockett, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 146)
- Romanus Maduabuchi, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 147)
- Katrina Molnar, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Keith Patterson, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Lori Peterson, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Allison Rainey, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Luke Roske, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Theodore Sturgeon, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Myung-Sahm Suh, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Ryan Thompson, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Rachel Timoner, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Julie Todd, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Islamic Internship for Worker Justice, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Mailing, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Paychecks, Employment forms, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- blank forms (non-employment) (Box 9, Folder 14)
- screeners questions for ss interviews, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Welcome packet #1, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Mailing #2, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- CST Interns, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- CST Debrief, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- UFCW-Smithfield, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- SEIU - Janitors Miami, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- SEIU- Janitors Houston, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- SEIU - Security D.C., 2006 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- SEIU - Janitors Chicago, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- SEIU - Local 509 - Group Home Boston, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- SEIU - security Boston, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Methodist Grant, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- SEIU - Janitors St. Louis, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- SEIU - Childcare Minneapolis, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- SEIU - Childcare Boston, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Sites, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- SS '01 Sites, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Philadelphia, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- AFSCME Council 31- Chicago, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Chicago UFCW, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Atlanta Sites, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Catholic Social Teaching Archives, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- SILC Forms Filled out (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Blueprints 4 Action (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Blueprints 4 Action, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Educational Materials, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Cenacle Retreat Center, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Expenses SS, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- North Park, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Recruitment mailing, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- UFCW - Smithfield Washington D.C., 2006 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- SEIU 32 BJ New York, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- UAW, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Unite Here - Boston, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Unite Here - Change to Win Chicago, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- AFL - CIO, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- AFSME Council 31 - Hospital Nurses Chicago, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- UAW Parking Production Ass. New York, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- UMWA - Peebody Coal Minders Louisville, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- UMWA Peabody Coal Miners Princeton, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- UMW - Peabody Coal Miners Terra Haute, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- New Orleans, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Mailings (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Seminary Summer Agenda, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Bus, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Bibliography/Reading List (Box 9, Folder 60)
- ICC, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- ICC Seminary Summer, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Prep Orientation, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Travel guidelines - SS, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Org. for Social Change Books (to order), 2006 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Evaluations - Orientation, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Seminary Summer + CST, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Restaurants, Kosher, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Shopping food/list, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Theological Reflection SS Chicago Interns - led by Sara Barb, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Housing Descriptions Seminar Summer, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Independent Study Example, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Theological Mentors, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Theological Reflection SS, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Training - Location, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- IIT Contract, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Publicity release forms, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- Campaign lit. - Sem. Summer, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 78)
- Debrief, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- Staff forms, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- Reflections - Internships, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Debrief, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 82)
- What you will leave behind, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 83)
- Internship eval: site, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 84)
- Internship eval: orientation/debrief, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 85)
- Meeting Rpt. Forms, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 86)
- Staff Role, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Protest Articles, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 88)
- Intern Info/for Debrief, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 89)
- A Seminary on Labor (Box 9, Folder 90)
- Media, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 91)
- Writings, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 92)
- Debrief Evaluations, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 93)
- Theo. Mentor Emergency Form, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 94)
- Expenses, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 95)
- Publicity Release, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 96)
- What Will I Leave Behind, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 97)
- Seminary Summer Prep For Debrief: "What will I leave behind", 2004 (Box 9, Folder 98)
- Seminary Summer Reflections, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 99)
- Seminary Summer Media, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 100)
- Evaluations Seminary Summer, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 101)
- Evaluations Reflections, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 102)
- AFL-CIO Nancy Lank, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 103)
- Our faith our work (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Labor Day, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Buddhist Labor Day Mailing (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Labor in Pulpits, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Labor Day, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Labor Day, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Labor Day, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Labor Day, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Labor Day, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Labor Day, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Labor Day, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Labor Day, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Jewish Labor Day Materials, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Labor in the Pulpits, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Labor Day, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Catholic Labor Materials, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Labor in the Pulpits, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- SC Ministry Foundation, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Faith Work Study Guide Publicity (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Avondale, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Local Interfaith Committee Press, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Sweat Shops, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Holiday Shopping, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Press Clips May-August, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Poultry Investigation - DC event, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Clue press clips, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Clips - general Background, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Clips: August - September, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Clips: October - December, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Code of Ethics Press, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Clips- Dec., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Labor in the Pulpits Kit (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Interfaith Procession LAX, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Pueblo (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Website Hits, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Union Literature, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Board and Staff Bios, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Sample Articles or Op-Eds, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Materials related to DHRMC/CHA contract, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Annual Reports, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Baltimore Sun Ad info, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Guest Worker Legislation, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Sweatshop petition signatures (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Gainesville background info, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Case Farms MSPA lawsuit, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- NC Poultry Justice Alliance Announced, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Worker Rights Board Hearing - UAS workers, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Worker Rights Board hearing - Acme workers, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Labor Day National, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Interfaith Committee Update, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Chicago Labor Day, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Melinda's Report, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Bathrooms, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Poultry Farms, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- DOL - FOI, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Morganton, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- CHW/CLUE event, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Worker Rights Manual Announcement, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Labor Day - National, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Chicago Labor Day, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- UFCW Convention Poultry Briefing, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Cross Border Blues report released, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Right to Organize, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Delmarva Poultry Justice Alliance festival, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Workers Memorial Day materials, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Monk poultry farm foreclosure, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- NC Poultry Justice Alliance Holy Week March, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Clips January-March, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- DOL Poultry Survey Results, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Delegation to Crown Headquarters in Baltimore, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Immokalee Tomato Growers Hunger Strike, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Employee Free Choice Act, 109th Congress, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Worker Memorial Day, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- September, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Morganton August, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Los Angeles, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Religion - Labor Conference, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Workers' Rights Board Hearing, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Workers' Rights Board Hearing, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Mt. Carmel's BHD SEIU Contract, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  Signing 3/29
- Hispanic Festival, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Building Guidelines Release, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Dept. Of Labor, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Bishop Pastoral on Poultry, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Winston Monk, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- New Economy Communications, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Georgia Congressional Visit, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Mike Leonard - UFCW (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Catchers, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Georgia Poultry Justice Alliance, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Gainesville, GA, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Burma, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- South Bend Case Farms, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Case Farms - Detroit, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Case Farms Cincinnati, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Case Farms NYC, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Unfinished Agenda, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- WFP Delegation Materials (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Case Farms Media Coverage, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Poultry Video, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Poultry Work, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Delmarva, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Whole Foods, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Case Farms Open Letter, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Case Farms - D.C. Event, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Code of Ethics Press Conference, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Morganton, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Tyson Cordon, IN Strike, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Delmarva, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Jewish Fund for Justice, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Marsh, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Rigoberta Menchu Tum, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Citizen Action, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Gainesville, Georgia, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Purchasers' Case Farms, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- North Carolina Goals, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Gainesville, Georgia, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Perdue, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Erickson's, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Gainesville, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Mary Geralyn (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Hudson Foods, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- House of Raeford, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Tyson Shareholder, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Tyson, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Tyson DOJ Indictment, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Commonwealth v. Bobo, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Poultry Week, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Koch Foods, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- The Cruelest Cuts, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Poultry Industry Overview, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- Texts of Social Creeds, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Living Wage, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Poor: New Deal, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Publications (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Sweatshop Watch, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Unionization, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Workplace Justice the Church, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Christian Research, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Training 2/06 budget, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- CST, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Bibliography, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Jewish Texts on Labor, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- CTU Presentation (Box 12, Folder 13)
- J-Term Resources, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Study Materials (religious), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Quizzes (Box 12, Folder 16)
- CAIR (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Episcopal AME, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Islamic Connections, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Jewish fund for Justice, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Jewish Social Justice Organizations (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Lutheran Materials, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Lutheran Youth Initiative (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Lutheran, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Muslim American Society Freedom Foundation (Box 12, Folder 25)
- United Church of Christ, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Economic Resources (Box 12, Folder 27)
- How Unions help all Workers, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- ECO - Justice Model, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Employment Project, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Engaging faculty (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Globalization, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Discussion Guidelines, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Interfaith, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- The Key to Effective Religious Dialogue, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Working Interfaith (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Media Clips, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Project Ideas Conf./Worker Sanctuary, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- New Ideas/Suggestions, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Catholic - Racism/Cultural Division, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Syllabi, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Ministry in an Urban Context, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Syllabi to Juan- Feb. 7, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Syllabi, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Globalization, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Christian Faith Economic Justice, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Churches and Economic Justice, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Church Work, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Christianity Social Justice, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Christianity and Social Justice, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Fact Book on Theological Education, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Coalition Building, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Connecting to the Broader Community (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Webmaster, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Key Websites, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Chapel Service Seminary, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Labor on the Bimah, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 56)
- Labor on the Minbar, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Worship Materials (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Rap lyrics from Willie Vandoren, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Worship, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Expense Religious Perspective, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Memo's- Liz, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Income Expenses, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Finance Reports, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Expenses, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Credit Card, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Sign-In Meetings, Conferences, Classes Attended, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 67)
- Worker Scenarios (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Contact, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Follow up Jan. 8th, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Contracts/Agreements with affiliate, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- To Read, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 72)
- Read perspective on Work-Economists Labor Catholics Public Policy, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 73)
- Proposed Steering Committee, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 74)
- Professors contacted/referred, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 75)
- Catholic Alliance Planning Meeting, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 76)
- Ascension Health, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Nimby Report, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Not in My Backyard, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Not in My Backyard (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Nimby mail copies to enclosed, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Unity Health, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- St. John's Medical, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Nimby to-do list, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Nimby, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- U.S. Catholic, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- 3rd Party wedge, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- St. Francis Associates, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Unions Can't Deliver, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Why Union Free, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Bad-mouthing Unions, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Warnings!, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Marymount, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Administration Education, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- SEIU strikes, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Strike Warnings, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Saint Joseph, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Unions want your money, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Robert F. Kennedy Medical Center, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Religious Interference, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Answering Employee Concerns, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Documentation from Unions, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Hold Off, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- House Calls, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Decency Principles, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- CST. Agency Shop, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Labor Organizing and Freedom of Association, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- From/On the Busters, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Following our Catholic social teachings, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Barrage of Material, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Kim on Religious Employer strategy, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Relationship Goal, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- 1st Health Care Dialogue, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Follow-up, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Religious Employers Strategy, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Tom Schindler, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- LCWR Conversations, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- LCWR Workshop, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Kitchen Cabinet, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Methodist Agenda, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- UMC Document (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Canadian Catholic Health, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- American Protestant Health Alliance, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Lutheran Agenda, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Mark Holman LSA, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Mercy Justice Team, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Annette McDermott, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Mary Elsbernd, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Julie Trocchio, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Catherin Pinkerton, CST Network, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- CHHSM Arelene Nehring, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Mary Hill, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- David Miller, SEIN, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Mike Place, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- A Fair and Just Workplace Process, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- A Fair and Just Workplace, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Open Letter from nuns on CHW, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Benedictine Health Services, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Franciscan Health Center, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- St. Francis Health Services, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Labor-Management Project, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Advisory Committee Correspondence, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Viewcrest, Duluth, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- August 01 Advisory, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Advisory Committee, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- December, 01, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Feb 02 Advisory, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Quarterly Reports, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- NACPA, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- National Register Publishing, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- NetBank, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- New World Publications, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- NC Workman's Comp Policy, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- NOA, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Nu-Century, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- NC Office Depot, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Office Max, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Office Report, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Ohm Bryz, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- PCS, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Parker Mailing Service, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Paychex Debits To Cash (Fee), 2000 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- TOMH Payroll Liabilities, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Personnel Concepts Ltd., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Phone Card(s), 2000 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Pitney Bowes, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Prime Telecommunications, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Princeton Insurance, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Prison Fellowship Ministries, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Quill, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Adjustments, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Sanford, Kristi Reimbursements etc., 2000 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Seminar Intern Summer, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Paul Sherry, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Special Offsite Services, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 57)